<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="article_legal_disclosure">
        \nHot Stuff does not provide legal, financial, or insurance advice. This page is written
        for informational purposes only, and is not a substitute for professional advice from a
        licensed attorney, financial advisor, or insurance professional.
    </string>
    <string name="article_getStarted">getStarted</string>
    <string name="article_getStarted_title">Walkthrough: Getting Started</string>
    <string name="article_getStarted_text">
        Welcome! This guide exists to provide a brief introduction to Hot Stuff\'s features and to
        explain the basic workflow of cataloging your possessions.

        \n\nFeatures
        \nHome: See charts and summaries of the items you have saved.

        \n\nItems: Scroll or search through saved items, export item records, and view, update, and
        delete saved items.

        \n\nCreate: Enter details, take photos, and save new records of your items.

        \n\nLearn: Learn about using Hot Stuff and read some additional perspectives on topics
        around the insurance claim process.

        \n\nSettings: Customize your experience by changing the app\'s theme, the preferred currency,
        and any building information.

        \n\nWorkflow
        \nStep 1: Tap the \'Create\' icon in the navigation bar at the bottom of the screen.

        \n\nStep 2: Fill in the required details for the item, including the name, quantity,
        category, and room. The rest of the form, including brand/manufacturer, item value,
        description, and a photo of
        the item, are all relevant, recommended information to include, but they aren\'t needed to
        save an item to your records.

        \n\nStep 3: Save the item to your records by pressing the \'Save Item\' button at the end of
        the form, a message should appear at the bottom of the screen when your item has been saved.

        \n\nStep 4: To save another item you can stay on the \'Create\' screen to begin the process
        again, however, if you wish to see your item or modify it\'s details, you can click
        on the \'Items\' icon in the navigation bar at the bottom of the screen to see a scrollable
        list of items you\'ve saved.

        \n\nStep 5: To modify your item, you can either scroll through the list until you
        find it, or you can tap the \'Search\' icon in the toolbar at the top of the screen to search
        your database for items with names, categories, rooms, and brands/manufacturers similar to
        what you type into the search bar.

        \n\nStep 6: To edit an item, you can tap the \'Edit\' button at the bottom of the
        screen to be taken to a screen similar to the \'Create\' items page. Any changes you make
        here can be saved by pressing the \'Save Changes\' button at the bottom of the screen, if
        you don\'t wish to change any of your item\'s details you can tap the back arrow icon at
        the top of the screen to return to the details page.

        \n\nStep 7: To delete an item, you can tap the \'Delete\' button at the bottom of the screen.
        A popup will appear asking if you\'re sure, if you press \'Delete\' again you\'ll be brought
        back to the \'Items\' screen and a message should appear at the bottom of the screen when
        your item has been deleted.

        \n\nThat\'s the basic flow of the app! If you want to export your item records, you can read
        more about it in the \'Exporting records\' walkthrough. If you find a bug or want to give
        some feedback you can tap the \'Options\' in the toolbar at the top of the screen to open a
        menu with those resources.

        \n\nLastly, if you have a question not answered here or need some further assistance, please
        visit our GitHub (linked in the \'About Hot Stuff\' section of the \'Learn\' screen), it
        should have resources and links to get in contact with the developer.
    </string>
    <string name="article_export">export</string>
    <string name="article_export_title">Walkthrough: Export Item Records</string>
    <string name="article_export_text">
        Follow these steps to export your data to a .CSV (Comma-Separated Values) file, which can
        then be opened in spreadsheet software like Google Sheets or Excel.

        \n\nStep 1: Navigate to the \'Items\' screen.

        \n\nStep 2: Tap the \'Export\' icon in the toolbar at the top of the screen.

        \n\nStep 3: A popup should appear prompting if you want to continue, press \'OK\'.

        \n\nStep 4: Wait for your data to download, a message should appear at the bottom of the
        screen when your items are successfully exported.

        \n\nStep 5: Check your device\'s downloads folder, your data should be there, named in this
        format: \'HS-DATA-[numbers].csv\'.

        \n\nStep 6: Using spreadsheet software like Google Sheets or Excel, open the
        file, you should see your item records organized into columns.

        \n\nStep 7: In that spreadsheet software, edit the rows, columns, or cells of the file if
        you notice any changes you need to make to your records.

        \n\nThat\'s it! You\'ve successfully exported your item records to a .CSV file using Hot
        Stuff. You can now use the file as a reference for personal records and for reporting claims
        to insurance providers!
    </string>
    <string name="article_whyCare">whyCare</string>
    <string name="article_whyCare_title">Hot Stuff: Simplify Your Fire Claims</string>
    <string name="article_whyCare_text">
        House fires are sudden, chaotic events, and while the thought of one breaking out may seem
        unlikely, a house fire is reported in the United States every 88 seconds¹.
        Unfortunately for many, the aftermath can be just as painful as the fire itself, because
        while fires burn out, their victim\'s trauma carries on. While only some suffer with
        the painful physical reminders of a fire, all deal with the heavy emotional strain that
        comes with the fear and anxiety of displacement or potential homelessness,
        losing their sense of safety and security, and the mounting stress that comes with the
        financial challenges of pulling their lives back together.

        \n\nThis is where we can help, because Hot Stuff isn\'t just about reacting to a crisis; it\'s
        about helping you avoid the worst of it. By using Hot Stuff to catalog your possessions in
        advance, you\'re creating a digital inventory that serves as a comprehensive record of your
        belongings. While the hope is that it is never necessary, if a fire occurs, having a
        specific, detailed catalog in advance can put you on the path to:
        \n\n1. Getting fair value for your possessions, without the influence of
        self-interested insurance companies or public adjusters
        \n\n2. Expediting your claims process, so you can get back to restoring what was lost sooner
        rather than later
        \n\n3. Having the peace of mind knowing your possessions are secured, leaving you to free to
        focus on what matters most in life: the stuff that money can\'t buy

        \n\nTaking the time to plan ahead for these unexpected, traumatic times can make a real
        difference when it matters most, because it\'s much easier to remember everything in a room
        when it\'s right there in front of you, than days or weeks later when it\'s all gone.
        Hot Stuff was created with this in mind, an app that people could trade a few rainy
        afternoons using, for the peace of mind knowing that if something were to happen, they
        would be better prepared for this horrific possibility.

        \n\nHot Stuff was designed ultimately to be an accessible tool, it requires no internet
        connection, collects no data, has no ads, is fully open sourced software, and perhaps most
        importantly, is completely free (but if you\'re reading this you already knew that)!
        If you find a bug, have an idea on how to improve the app, want to help translate or to
        contribute in some other way, please get in touch! Community feedback is always welcomed
        and encouraged.

        \n\nSadly, Hot Stuff is not a one-stop shop for all of someone\'s needs after a fire.
        While we can\'t protect people from suffering the injustice and heartache of losing where
        they live, we are grateful and proud to be of assistance (for at least our small part) of
        the long, challenging road back home.

        \n\n\nSources:
        \n1. Hall, S. (November 2023). Fire loss in the United States During 2022.
        Quincy, MA:National Fire Protection Association.
    </string>

    <string name="article_detail">detail</string>
    <string name="article_detail_title">Attention to Detail: Why it Matters</string>
    <string name="article_detail_text">
        In the face of the unexpected, having a detailed home inventory is an essential part of
        having a smooth and successful experience when filing insurance claims. Every home is filled
        with valued possessions and taking the time to make records of them ensures that when
        disaster strikes they can accurately be accounted for.

        \n\nAttention to detail is the linchpin in accurately valuing possessions. Providing
        specific, precise details, like serial number, model name, manufacturer, price, receipt, etc.
        ensures that an insurance provider cannot undervalue a policyholder\'s belongings.

        \n\nThe most efficient way to create a home inventory is by approaching it systematically.
        Opening every drawer, every cabinet, and moving through the house, finishing one room and
        then moving on to the next. Not only does this help ensure complete coverage, but it also
        makes the challenge more manageable.

        \n\nA home inventory is an ongoing process, not a one-time task, it\'s okay if it takes
        several days, weeks, or months to finish. However, when finished it is important to stay on
        top of updating the inventory, ideally a few times a year, to avoid forgetting about details
        when adding new items or remembering to remove old ones.
        Keeping an inventory current guarantees that coverage remains reflective of a home\'s true
        value, and strengthens a policyholder\'s case during the claims process.

        \n\nSome policyholders focus only on the larger, more expensive items, which is fair, people
        have a lot of stuff, and recording all of it can be a time-consuming process. However, it is
        important to remember that the little, mundane things in life can add up very quickly.

        \n\nIn a total loss most people may forget about or skip over bathrooms entirely, and yet
        they would likely be missing out on hundreds of dollars of losses. Life has gotten to be so
        expensive, consider the cost of:

        \n\nshampoos,
        \nlotions,
        \nconditioner,
        \nscale,
        \nsoap dispenser,
        \ntoilet brush,
        \nhairdryer,
        \nbath mat,
        \nshower curtain,
        \ncurtain liner,
        \ncurtain rod,
        \ncurtain rings,
        \nplunger,
        \nsoap bars,
        \nmedications,
        \ntrash can,
        \ntowels,
        \ntoothpaste,
        \nrazors,
        \nhairbrushes,
        \nnail clippers,
        \nmouthwash,
        \ntoothbrushes, etc.

        \n\nThink of all the different items not mentioned here, and imagine trying to remember all
        of them and more a few days after your life has fallen apart. These mundane items can be a
        pain to record now, but again, they add up quick.

        \n\nA final note, when recording more expensive items policyholders should
        check to make sure that the items they\'re recording are worth more than their coverage limits,
        and if so, deciding whether the want to schedule property endorsements with their insurance
        provider to cover the full amount of those specific items. While they increase premiums, the
        limits on things like jewelry, clothing, liquor, antiques, collectibles, etc. tend to be pretty low, so it\'s a
        conversation worth having if a policyholder can afford it.
    </string>

    <string name="article_likeKind">likeKind</string>
    <string name="article_likeKind_title">Like Kind and Quality</string>
    <string name="article_likeKind_text">
        \'Like kind and quality\' refers to a principle that, in the event of a covered loss, the
        insurance provider is obligated to replace or repair the damaged property with items of a
        similar nature and value. This principle ensures that policyholders are not left with
        inferior replacements or repairs after a covered incident.

        \n\nNot all insurance policies bind providers to the principle, as such policyholders may
        want to familiarize themselves with the language specific to their policy, as different
        providers can have different terms, definitions, and conditions of coverage.

        \n\nLying on an insurance claim is a terrible idea, it is both illegal and can cause
        policyholders even bigger problems (such as invalidating entire claims). However,
        sometimes it may make sense not to be forthcoming with the entire truth; Particularly with
        items that possess unique or specific features that contribute to their value, and may not
        have equivalents in the market that perfectly match their distinct characteristics.

        \n\nFor example, a vintage watch, a custom-made piece of furniture, a high-resolution camera,
        or a rare collectible are all likely to have a combination of niche features that are
        difficult for insurance providers to easily find replacements for on the open market. A
        policyholder that strongly insists on a fair replacement for those features, with calm,
        clear reasoning for their position, may find that the replacement cost of a comparable item
        is likely to be fairly expensive, potentially more expensive than the appraised value of a
        specific, very detailed item.
    </string>

    <string name="article_jargonGlossary">jargon</string>
    <string name="article_jargonGlossary_title">Glossary of Insurance Jargon</string>
    <string name="article_jargonGlossary_text">
        Fire insurance policies can be a difficult, complicated read if you aren\'t an insurance
        industry professional. This glossary exists as an optional resource if you want help
        understanding some of the terms you may have seen within the details of a fire insurance
        policy or other related documents. Please note, the information provided below is meant to
        serve as a general guide, it only covers the context of fire insurance, and is not exhaustive.
        Different types of insurance and insurance providers may have varied interpretations,
        definitions, or alternatives to the terms listed below.

        \n\nIf you notice any discrepancies or feel unsure about any specific details of your policy,
        you should seek clarification right away to avoid potential issues during a claim. Insurance
        providers can use tricky language, so do your best to stay informed, review your policy regularly,
        and make adjustments as needed to maintain your desired level of coverage for your property.

        \n\nA
        \n\nAccident
        \nAn unforeseen act or result that may cause property damage. In some
        policies, it is identified as occurring at a specific time and place. In others, it
        includes continuous or repeated exposure to the same conditions.

        \n\nAct of God (also known as a Catastrophe)
        \nAn event caused by the forces of nature, without human intervention and which could not
        have been prevented by reasonable action on behalf of the policyholder; for example, floods,
        tornadoes, earthquakes, hurricanes, etc.

        \n\nActual Cash Value
        \nThe market value of lost or damaged property at the time of loss. This is generally in
        contrast with another, more expensive form of reimbursement: replacement cost. Payout is
        calculated as the actual cost of replacing property minus depreciation.

        \n\nAdditional living expense
        \nCoverage that provides a specified amount per day for additional expenses in the event
        that you cannot live in your insured residence.

        \n\nAdhesion
        \nA special characteristic of most insurance contracts. Has non-negotiable terms set by the
        insurance provider for which the purchasing customer may only accept or reject.

        \n\nAgent
        \nAn individual who acts as a representative of the provider and sells insurance, usually on
        a commission basis. Generally, there are two types: exclusive (who sell for only
        one provider), and non-exclusive (who sell for multiple).

        \n\nAmendment (also known as an Endorsement)
        \nA statement added to an insurance policy that alters, deletes or adds coverage, terms or
        provisions of the policy.

        \n\nAppraisal
        \nAn evaluation process that determines the value of property, or the extent of damage,
        usually performed by an authorized, impartial expert.

        \n\nArson
        \nIntentional and malicious burning of property.

        \n\nB
        \n\nC

        \n\nCancellation
        \nThe termination of a policy before its expiration date.

        \n\nCatastrophe (also known as an Act of God)
        \nA sudden, severe disaster that results in a large amount of damage affecting a specific
        geographic area; for example: hurricanes, floods, tornadoes, etc.

        \n\nClaim
        \nA request for payment under a single item of coverage on an insurance policy.

        \n\nClaimant
        \nThe policyholder making a claim.

        \n\nClaims Representative (also known as an Inside Adjuster)
        \nAn employee at an insurance provider who handles a policyholder\'s claim.

        \n\nClaimed Expenses
        \nA request for payment for a claimant\'s out of pocket expenses.

        \n\nCondition
        \nUsed to describe the general maintenance and upkeep of property.

        \n\nConditions
        \nThe section or sections of a policy that explains the duties and responsibilities of the
        policyholder and the insurance provider.

        \n\nConstruction type
        \nThe construction of the insured building; there are two common types for homes: frame
        (wood, drywall, insulation) and masonry (bricks, stones, concrete blocks).

        \n\nCoverage
        \nThe protections and benefits provided to a policyholder by an insurance provider, as
        outlined in an insurance contract.

        \n\nD

        \n\nDamage
        \nLoss or harm to property.

        \n\nDeclarations (also known as a Dec Page)
        \nThe section of the policy that includes a summary of your policy, including personal and
        related information such as your name and address; the property that is being insured, its
        location and description; the policy period; the amount of insurance coverage, applicable
        premiums, etc.

        \n\nDefensible space
        \nA buffer between buildings on a property and any long grass, trees, shrubs, or wildland area
        surrounding them. Acts to minimize the radiant heat exposure and pathways wildfire can burn,
        creating a barrier between the surrounding area and any structures on the property. In the US,
        fire-prone areas tend to require anywhere between one to two-hundred feet of space.

        \n\nDeductible
        \nThe portion of a claim you pay out of pocket. Generally, choosing a higher deductible will
        lower your insurance premiums.

        \n\nDepreciation
        \nThe decrease in value of any property due to age, wear and tear, or other related factors.

        \n\nDwelling
        \nThe section of a policy that covers the physical structure of the primary residence of a
        property.

        \n\nE

        \n\nEndorsement (also known as an Amendment)
        \nA provision or document added to an insurance policy that changes the original coverage
        offered in the policy.

        \n\nEquity
        \nPercent of a policy paid.

        \n\nEstimate
        \nAn assessment of the cost to repair any damaged property.

        \n\nExclusions
        \nThe section of an insurance policy that excludes coverage for certain risks, persons,
        properties, or locations.

        \n\nF

        \n\FAIR (Fair Insurance Requirements) Plan
        \nA program to make fire and other forms of property insurance available to homeowners who
        may have difficulty obtaining coverage from insurance providers for a variety of reasons;
        including: being in areas prone to natural disasters, high-crime, being in disrepair,
        or having many previous claims.

        \n\nField Appraiser (also known as a Field Adjuster)
        \nAn insurance representative who works primarily outside, often meeting
        with policyholders face-to-face. Typical responsibilities include scene investigations,
        negotiations with claimants, and conducting damage inspections.

        \n\nFire insurance
        \nThe section of a homeowner\'s policy that insures against direct loss by fire, smoke, and other
        defined causes. Most have coverage for wildfires, but this is not always the case in
        fire-prone areas.

        \n\nFloater insurance
        \nA type of policy that covers personal property as it moves anywhere within a specified
        territory; provides additional coverage over what normal insurance policies do not.

        \n\nG
        \n\nH

        \n\nHazard
        \nSituations or conditions that increases the possibility or extent of a loss; for example:
        supplemental heating devices, old wiring, smokers living in the residence, further distance
        from fire stations, etc.

        \n\nHomeowner
        \nAn individual who owns and does not rent their residence.

        \n\nHousehold Member
        \nFamily members or individuals living within the policyholder\'s residence.

        \n\nI

        \n\nImprovements and Betterments
        \nAdditions or changes made by a lessee or renter at their expense which enhance
        the value of the occupied building. These become part of the realty (and are not legally
        subject to removal) and require special insurance consideration.

        \n\nIndemnity
        \nThe insurance principle of putting the insured back in the same (or similar) financial
        position after a loss as he or she was in before the loss occurred.

        \n\nIndependent Adjuster
        \nA third-party contractor hired by an insurance provider to evaluating insurance claims to
        determine (and if possible, minimize) the provider\'s liability.

        \n\nInside Adjuster (also known as a Claims Representative)
        \nAn employee at an insurance provider who handles a policyholder\'s claim.

        \n\nInsurable Interest
        \nAny interest in a subject, or any legal relation to it, of such a nature that a certain
        event (such as fire) might cause monetary loss requiring insurance.

        \n\nInsurance Provider (also known as an Insurer, or Insurance Company)
        \nAn organization that provides insurance.

        \n\nInsured
        \nA person or organization covered by an insurance policy.

        \n\nInsuring Agreements
        \nThe part or parts of an insurance policy that state the various coverages provided.

        \n\nJ
        \n\nK
        \n\nL

        \n\nLapse
        \nA period of time when someone goes without insurance coverage.

        \n\nLease
        \nA contract granting use or occupation of property during a specified period, in exchange
        for a specified rent.

        \n\nLeaseholder
        \nAn individual who possesses or has use of property through a lease.

        \n\nLessee
        \nAn individual to whom a lease is granted.

        \n\nLien
        \nAn underlying claim on property as a security for the payment of a debt or completion of duty.

        \n\nLienholder
        \nThe person or organization with a claim against property until some debt is paid off or
        duty completed; generally the mortgage lender, such as a bank, credit union, or other type
        of financial institution.

        \n\nLimit
        \nThe maximum amount of protection provided by the insurance provider to the policyholder for
        a specific coverage.

        \n\nLimit of Liability (also known as Limits of Insurance)
        \nThe maximum amount an insurance provider will pay for a covered loss, as stated in the
        policyholder\'s policy.

        \n\nLoss
        \nA measurable cost of direct and/or accidental damage to an insured property; the
        basis for filing a claim.

        \n\nLoss History
        \nA record of prior claims the policyholder has filed.

        \n\nLoss of Use
        \nCompensation for losses the policyholder incurs due to the inability to use their property.

        \n\nM

        \n\nMisrepresentation
        \nWritten or verbal statements that are misleading or untrue.

        \n\nMitigation
        \nSteps taken to prevent or reduce the amount or likelihood of loss.

        \n\nMonoline
        \nA policy written to cover a single line of insurance; for example: fire, flood,
        earthquake, etc.

        \n\nN

        \n\nNamed insured (also known as a policyholder)
        \nThe person or persons insured by the insurance policy. The names are listed on the
        declarations page within the policy.

        \n\nNamed perils
        \nCovered hazards that are listed in an insurance policy.

        \n\nNon-Renewal
        \nWhen an insurance provider decides not to renew a policy at the end of its policy period;
        providers are required to notify policyholders prior to dropping their coverage.

        \n\nO

        \n\nOccupancy
        \nThe number of people living at the property, and whether they live there full-time.

        \n\nOccurrence
        \nAn event, or repeated exposure to conditions, which unexpectedly causes injury or damage
        during the policy period.

        \n\nOutbuildings (also known as Other Structures)
        \nA structure located on the residence premises that is not directly attached to the
        dwelling structure; for example: sheds, fences, detached garages, etc.

        \n\nP

        \n\nPeril
        \nA cause of a possible accident, loss, or claim; for example: power surges, falling debris,
        lightning strikes, etc.

        \n\nPersonal property
        \nTangible property that is not land, connected to land, and is movable in some way; for
        example: furniture, appliances, electronics, etc. Standard policies limits the amount you can
        claim per item, so policyholders may wish to acquire additional coverage to schedule
        higher-value property items.

        \n\nPolicy
        \nA formal written contract for insurance between an insurance provider and a policyholder.

        \n\nPolicy expiration date
        \nThe date the policy period ends; generally found on the declarations page, insurance card,
        and any cancellation or policy renewal notices.

        \n\nPolicy period
        \nThe length of time your policy is active and coverage is provided for.

        \n\nPolicyholder (also known as the named insured)
        \nThe person or persons insured by the insurance policy. The names are listed on the
        declarations page within the policy.

        \n\nPremium
        \nThe price of the policy that a insurance provider charges in return for providing coverage
        to the policyholder. Not to be confused with a rate.

        \n\nProof of Loss
        \nA statement made regarding the extent of the claim; it may be requested in accordance with
        the conditions of the policy.

        \n\nProperty
        \nAnything that has value; there are two types: real property and personal property.

        \n\nProperty fire wall
        \nA physical wall with qualities of fire resistance and structural stability. Designed to
        control the spread of a fire.

        \n\nProtective devices
        \nSafety equipment designed to prevent, protect or notify you in the event of an emergency;
        for example: fire extinguishers, dead-bolt locks, fire alarms, smoke alarms and burglar alarms.

        \n\nProximate Cause
        \nAn act or omission initiating an unbroken sequence of events resulting in damage to property.

        \n\nPublic adjuster (also known as private adjusters)
        \nAn third-party professional hired by a policyholder to help settle an insurance claim on
        their behalf, generally for a flat percentage of the final claim settlement payout.

        \n\nQ
        \n\nR

        \n\nRate
        \nThe base rating units used to determine a policyholder\'s premium.

        \n\nRating
        \nThe determination of premium to be charged for coverage on a risk based upon risk
        characteristics and actuarial calculations on the chance of loss.

        \n\nReal property
        \nLand and the permanent things attached to, embedded in, or growing on it; for example:
        buildings, outdoor fixtures, machinery, etc.

        \n\nRelease
        \nA legally binding contract stating that all obligations past, present or future arising
        from a particular accident or occurrence have been fulfilled.

        \n\nRenewal
        \nA policy issued to replace one that will expire by a certain date.

        \n\nRenters Insurance
        \nA type of property insurance providing coverage to an individual living in an apartment,
        condominium or single family home owned by someone else.

        \n\nReplacement cost
        \nThe cost to repair or replace property with to the same standard and quality. This is in
        contrast with a cheaper form of reimbursement called Actual Cash Value. Payout is calculated
        as the cost of replacing property up to a limit of liability.

        \n\nResidence premises
        \nThe physical location of the property for which insurance coverage is provided.

        \n\nRisk
        \nThe chance of suffering a loss.

        \n\nS

        \n\nSalvage
        \nDamaged property which is taken over by the insurance provider after payment of a claim.

        \n\nScheduled Property
        \nA listing of personal property items that are insured for a specific amount to that item’s
        full value; for example: jewelry, art, designer clothes, etc. Items are usually scheduled
        when they are higher in value and subject to limits of liability within the policy that are
        lower than their value.

        \n\nStatute of Limitation
        \nA specified time period during which a policyholder can file a claim for damages, if
        this period ends without a filed claim, you will not be able to get reimbursement. The
        length of time you have to file varies depending on the territory the policy is in.

        \n\nSub-limit
        \nA specified amount less than the maximum limits on a policy. Sub-limits are noted for
        specified coverages or types of property.

        \n\nSubrogation
        \nInsurance provider\'s right to legally pursue damages from a third party that caused an
        insurance loss to the policyholder.

        \n\nSupplement (also known as a Supplemental Estimate)
        \nUsed to cover damage not included in the original estimate.
        \nAdditional estimate of repair costs revealed after the initial assessment was done.

        \n\nSupplemental heating device
        \nA fuel-burning appliance used as secondary heating source; for example: wood, coal and pellet
        stoves, freestanding fireplaces, etc. Residences with them tend to require special
        requirements be met to be insurable. Small, portable space heating devices are generally not
        considered supplemental heating devices.

        \n\nSurcharge
        \nA temporary increase in a premium that is assessed as a penalty to compensate
        insurance providers for increased risk. They are usually added when providers identify
        behavior they deem to be risky to insure, like missing payments, filing an excessive number
        of claims, having lapses in your insurance coverage, etc.

        \n\nT

        \n\nTotal Loss
        \nProperty that has sustained damage so extensive that rebuilding or replacing it is less
        expensive than repairing it into safe, working order (depending on area regulations). Payout
        is generally the limit of liability on the property.

        \n\nU

        \n\nUnderwriting
        \nThe process an insurance provider uses to determine if someone is eligible for insurance
        and, if so, how much that person should pay for insurance.

        \n\nV
        \n\nW

        \n\nWear and Tear
        \nGeneral or nonspecific damage that builds up over time.

        \n\nX
        \n\nY
        \n\nZ
    </string>

    <string name="article_adjusters">adjusters</string>
    <string name="article_adjusters_title">Public Adjusters: Pros and Cons</string>
    <string name="article_adjusters_text">
    Dealing with insurance claims can be a daunting task by itself, and it is often made even worse
    by the heartache and stress that comes in the aftermath of major damage. When facing this
    challenge policyholders often find themselves at a crossroads: should they navigate the difficult
    process alone or enlist the assistance of a public adjuster? While public adjusters can offer
    valuable expertise, it\'s crucial to understand both the advantages and drawbacks before
    deciding to hire one.

    \n\nPros:

    \n\nMaximizing Compensation
    \nThe biggest advantage of hiring a public adjuster is their expertise. They do this through
    industry knowledge; such as knowing where to look for potential missed damage or how best to
    create records of what was lost; and through negotiation, to maximize their client\'s best
    possible settlement.

    \n\nGuidance
    \nPublic adjusters have an in-depth knowledge of the claims processes. An adjuster\'s expertise
    can help them translate jargon and legalese so clients can better understand the details of their
    policies.

    \n\nTime and Stress Relief
    \nManaging an insurance claim can be a stressful and time-consuming process. Public adjusters
    handle the paperwork, communication, and negotiations, allowing their clients to focus on
    putting their lives back together.

    \n\nDisputes
    \nPublic adjusters can review and renegotiate settlements if a policyholder is unhappy with their
    insurance provider\'s initial offer.

    \n\nCons:

    \n\nCost
    \nThe largest drawback of hiring a public adjuster, the cost is usually between 5% to 20% of the
    final settlement, or in some cases, a flat or hourly rate. While some areas may cap the total
    fee an adjuster can receive, and some adjusters are open to negotiating their fees, policyholders
    everywhere need to weigh the benefits adjusters provide with the costs, which are paid directly
    from their payouts.

    \n\nSuitability
    \nNot every insurance claim warrants the involvement of a public adjuster. For smaller or
    uncomplicated claims, it is likely more cost-effective for policyholders to handle them by
    themselves, avoiding the added expense the adjuster will make on their settlement. In fact,
    some adjusters will even refuse claims below a certain level of payout, so it\'s crucial that
    policyholders assess the complexity of their claim before deciding whether a public adjuster is
    necessary.

    \n\nPayout Limits
    \nPublic adjusters cannot get more money for their clients from insurance providers than they
    have coverage for in their policy. The limit of insurance or limit of liability in a policy is
    the maximum amount a policyholder can receive, and it\'s extremely unlikely a public adjuster
    will be able to negotiate a settlement above that amount.

    \n\nClaim Processing Delays
    \nHiring a public adjuster often extends how long it takes for claims to be processed, as they
    negotiate back and forth with the insurance provider over the final settlement amount. Generally,
    the more complicated the claim, the longer it will take for a public adjuster and provider to
    hash out the details, extending the period a policyholder has to wait for their payout by weeks
    or months.

    \n\nAvailability and Validity
    \nOnly some areas require public adjusters to be licensed, in others no qualifications are
    required at all, which can lead to vulnerable people being taken advantage of. When hiring an
    adjuster policyholders should make sure they fully understand the details of the contract and
    the structure of fees before signing anything.

    \n\nUltimately, hiring a public adjuster can be a strategic move, but it\'s essential for
    policyholders to carefully consider if the circumstances of their claim are appropriate for the
    cost of professional assistance.
    </string>

    <string name="article_acknowledgements">acknowledgements</string>
    <string name="article_acknowledgements_title">Acknowledgements</string>
    <string name="article_acknowledgements_text">
        We use the following open source libraries, modules, and frameworks to make Hot Stuff:

        \n\nAndroidX modules
        \nCore KTX
        \nLifecycle KTX
        \nLiveData KTX
        \nNavigation KTX

        \n\nJetpack libraries
        \nAppCompat
        \nCardView
        \nPreference
        \nRecyclerView

        \n\nTesting
        \nAndroidX Test
        \nEspresso
        \nJUnit4

        \n\nMiscellaneous
        \nAndroid ConstraintLayout
        \nMaterial Components for Android
        \ncom.github.PhilJay:MPAndroidChart
    </string>
</resources>